[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "628611a542e33a304d4070f1"
  },
  "question": "React is mainly used for building ___.",
  "answer": [
    "Database",
    "Connectivity",
    "User interface"
  ],
  "correct": 3
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6286152542e33a304d4070f4"
  },
  "question": "What is ReactJS?",
  "answer": [
    "Library for building interaction interfaces",
    "User-interface framework",
    "Server side Framework"
  ],
  "correct": 1
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6286236c42e33a304d4070f5"
  },
  "question": "Choose the right answer about JSX.",
  "answer": [
    "JSX provides expressiveness of JavaScript along with HTML, like template syntax",
    "JSX is a syntax notation for JavaScript XML",
    "All of the above options"
  ],
  "correct": 3
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "628623e542e33a304d4070f6"
  },
  "question": "How to write an HTML Comment ?",
  "answer": [
    "<!-- This is an HTML comment -->",
    "/* This is an HTML comment */",
    "// This is an HTML comment"
  ],
  "correct": 1
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "628624d342e33a304d4070f7"
  },
  "question": "The arbitrary inputs of components are called ___.",
  "answer": [
    "Props",
    "Elements",
    "Keys"
  ],
  "correct": 1
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "628625ab42e33a304d4070f8"
  },
  "question": "Inside which element do you put JavaScript?",
  "answer": [
    "<var> ",
    "<section> ",
    "<script> "
  ],
  "correct": 3
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6286263242e33a304d4070f9"
  },
  "question": "Which one of the following is correct?",
  "answer": [
    "i =+ 1;",
    "i += 1;",
    "i = i++1;"
  ],
  "correct": 2
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "628626be42e33a304d4070fa"
  },
  "question": "How do you get cookies in JavaScript?",
  "answer": [
    "document.cookie",
    "location.cookies",
    "document.cookies"
  ],
  "correct": 1
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6286276942e33a304d4070fc"
  },
  "question": "How do you open a new window with JavaScript?",
  "answer": [
    "open(new window());",
    "window.new(...);",
    "window.open(...);"
  ],
  "correct": 3
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "628628eb42e33a304d4070fd"
  },
  "question": "What is called the functions with no return value?",
  "answer": [
    "Procedures",
    "Method",
    "Dynamic function"
  ],
  "correct": 1
}]